

Pezhman Ghavami

Front-End Engineer

☑ mail@pezhmanghavami.com

♠ pezhmanghavami.com

github.com/pezhmanghavami

Abut Me

Over the past four years, I co-founded Rayabot and started my professional journey as a developer; During this time, I took various ideas into production, and solving such a wide variety of problems gave me a good understanding of different parts of an applications stack. The result of these experiences leads to my growing interest in Front-End and a passion for building and delivering intuitive user experiences!

Experience

Co-Founder and Full-Stack Developer - Rayabot ☐

May 2017- February 2022

2019-2021

Worked with a team of developers and designers to build a SaaS product which included:

- A user control panel for managing subscriptions
- An admin control panel to manage users and the instances of our automated trading software
- Product performance data visualization in the admin panel
- An SSE server for broadcasting our trading software's server instance events to the clients
- A client in the cTrader platform as a cBot
- A GUI made using electron to act as a bridge client for MetaTrader React • Redux-Toolkit • React Router • Sass • Styled Components • D3.js • Electron • Express.js • PostgreSQL • Redis • JavaScript • C# • cAlgo • MQL5

2019

Made an internal REST API for authenticating and managing our various trading software.

Express.js • JavaScript

2018

Made a WordPress e-commerce website.

WordPress

2017-2022

Closely collaborated with the trading team to turn their strategies into indicators and automated trading solutions in the cAlgo platform.

cAlgo • C#

2017-2022

Made several telegram bots for broadcasting indicator signals, delivering trade notifications, and monitoring different trading software statuses.

Node.js • Prisma • SQLite • JavaScript • TypeScript

Skills

Programming Languages

JavaScript (ES6), TypeScript, HTML, CSS/Sass

Libraries & Frameworks

React.js, Next.js, Redux Toolkit, React Router, Prisma, SWR, React Query, Tailwindcss, Styled Components, Zustand, D3.js, Socket.io, ws, Jest, Cypress, tRPC, Express.js, Node.js

Tools & Platforms

Git, Webpack, Vite, Netliy, Firebase, Vercel, Docker, Github Actions

Projects

Clothing Shop ☑

A prototype e-commerce website built with Next.js, React, Tailwindcss, SWR, Prisma and TypeScript

Chat App ☐

A prototype chat application built using PERN stack, reactrouter, SWR, Prisma and Socket.io

Sorting Visualizer <a>□

A web app to visualize different sorting algorithms

Education

Azad University

Sep 2016 - Jun 2020

Information Technology